jayde.com 2002-12-07

# iEntry Corporate | Privacy Policy

The iEntry, Inc. Privacy Policy  
Recognized by the industry for our commitment to safeguarding consumer privacy on our Web site, we operate under a strict set of privacy principles: 

The only information the iEntry Network obtains about individual visitors to its Web site is information supplied voluntarily by visitors.

In cases when the iEntry Network may need personal information to provide visitors with services tailored especially for them, or to inform them about new features or services, visitors are asked explicitly for that information. 

All identifiable information provided by members (name, email or home address) will not be disclosed to anyone unless members specifically request the iEntry Network to do so. 

Only statistical information of our members as a group (usage habits, demographics) may be shared with any partner of the iEntry Network; no identifiable information will be shared at any time. 

The iEntry Network employs strict security measures to safeguard online transactions; personal information is stored in a secured database and always sent via an encrypted Internet channel. 

Delete/DeActivate Policy  
Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter. While all efforts are made to insure this information is viewable in all email browsers, there may be cases where certain email browsers do not display the unsubscribe information correctly. In such cases subscribers may also adjust their subscriber settings by logging into our Member Area at [http://members.ientrymail.com](http://members.ientrymail.com/). If you are having problems unsubscribing please forward the entire newsletter to [abuse@ientry.com](mailto:abuse@ientry.com) and you will be removed within 1 business day. Please note that direct replies to any newsletter are processed by computer and are not viewed by a human. To comment on a particular newsletter please use the comments@ address included in the newsletter.

E-newsletter Privacy Policy  
iEntry maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. Your information, including your e-mail address will not be given to any third party if you sign up for one of our newsletters. If you sign up for an e-mail newsletter at an iEntry site, you will receive the e-mail newsletter you have requested and our house newsletter eZined. eZined promotes our new newsletter offerings and you can unsubscribe from it at any time.

Advertising  
iEntry newsletters may contain 3rd party advertising. As part of your subscription, we may send out occasional special newsletter issues featuring one of our advertising partners. Such issues will generally feature some product or service that we believe will be of interest to our subscribers. Instructions for unsubscribing from these issues will be included with each mailing. You may decline from receiving these special mailings and still continue to receive our regular issues.

Polling  
Several iEntry sites offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what the iEntry audience thinks about important issues. iEntry uses a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users. 

Surveys  
Occasionally, iEntry conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party. 

Submission  
Our site submission guidelines are simple and straightforward. Multiple submissions of the same site, site descriptions with embedded graphics and/or javascript, pornographic site submissions and sites promoting hatred, intolerance, or prejudice are not permitted and will be deleted during or after our filtering process. Spamming the directory is a waste of everyone's time. It entails considerable work on our part to remove duplicate listings and consequently delays the posting of legitimate submissions for a period of 4 to 5 weeks following the date of submission.

Tracking .Gif’s  
iEntry Inc. and its advertisers may use tracking or single-pixel gif images to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. iEntry Inc. does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Some advertisers may use tracking gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer.

Consent  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by iEntry Inc. as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

For additional detail regarding iEntry's site submission guidelines, please visit our FAQ page.

How to Reach Us  
If you ever feel uncertain about whether this site is following the privacy policy we have described here, please notify us by e-mail to [abuse@ientry.com](mailto:abuse@ientry.com). We will make every reasonable effort to find and correct the problem promptly.
